Guide to the Montana Department of Environmental Quality, Director's Office records 1908-2002
Montana Historical Society
- Subject Files
  - Bridger Pines Subdivision, Gallatin County (re: sewage lagoon), 1976 (Box-folder 41/25)
  - Butte, Silver Bow Annex Nursing Home, 1972 (Box-folder 41/26)
  - Buttrey's Food Stores (Great Falls) (re: variance), 1970 (Box-folder 41/27)
  - Canyon Hotel, Columbia Falls (Legal Materials), 1973 (Box-folder 41/28)
  - Cascade County, Great Falls wastewater, 1979 (Box-folder 41/29)
  - Cascade County, Great Falls Refuse Disposal area (Hearing), 1972-1974 (Box-folder 41/30)
  - Conoco Inc., Air Quality Permit (Testimony, Briefs, etc.), 1990 (Box-folder 42/1-3)
  - CENEX, CENEX-EXXON (Variances, Notices of Violation, Sulfur Dioxide, Farmers Union Central Exchange), 1973-1982 (Box-folder 42/4-7)
  - Circle West Project (McCone County), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 42/8)
  - Chemical Dependency, Alcoholism (infirmaries, In-patient, out-patient, facilities, state plan), 1974 (Box-folder 42/9)
  - Clark Fork Valley Hospital (Plains, MT) (re: Hearing on disapproval of Certificate of Need for Construction of long-term care beds), 1978 (Box-folder 42/10)
  - Colstrip, Montana Power Company (includes Construction permit and modifications, legal actions, Northern Plains Resource Council, Units 3 and 4), 1974-1981 (Box-folder 42/11-23)
  - Continental Oil Company, Billings (variance), 1972, 1976 (Box-folder 42/24-25)
  - Comola, Billo and Linda vs. Lyle Grenager (Sanders Co.), 1976 (Box-folder 43/1)
  - Del Connor Lumber (includes variance app.), 1971-1973 (Box-folder 43/2)
  - Developmentally Disabled, Community Homes, 1973 (Box-folder 43/3)
  - Douglas (Wesley) Subdivision, 1979 (Box-folder 43/4)
  - Dugdale Construction Company, Air Quality Permit 1979 (Box-folder 43/5)
  - Dupuis Brothers Lumber, 1970 (Box-folder 43/6)
  - Empire Sand and Gravel, Variance, 1971 (Box-folder 43/7)
  - EXXON (includes CENEX hearing), 1976 (Box-folder 43/8)
  - Farmers Union GTA, Variance, 1971 (Box-folder 43/9)
  - Feedlots (includes Regulations), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 43/10-12)
  - Flathead County Refuse, Variance, 1975 (Box-folder 43/13)
  - Flint Valley Forest Products, 1974 (Box-folder 43/14)
  - Flor-Haven Home, Hearing, 1970 (Box-folder 43/15-16)
  - Food Service Establishments, Rule Appeal and Adoption, 1979 (Box-folder 43/17)
  - Fort Ponderosa, 1978 (Box-folder 43/18)
  - Friendship Villa, Miles City (transcript), 1977 (Box-folder 43/19)
  - Glasgow AFB Hearing (transcript), 1974 (Box-folder 43/20)
  - Glendive Community Hospital Hearing (Incinerator) (transcript), 1976 (Box-folder 43/21)
  - Golden Glacier, Duck Lake (EIS), 1977 (Box-folder 43/22)
  - W.R. Grace and Company, Variance hearings (transcript), 1970-1974 (Box-folder 43/23)
  - Great Falls, Deaconess Hospital (Obstetrical beds, Proposal to install Axial Tomography Scanner), 1975 (Box-folder 43/24-25)
  - Forest Park Trailer Court Hearing (transcript), 1975 (Box-folder 43/26)
  - Hotel Hearing Notices (Rainbow, Beaudry, and Midtown Hotel), 1975 (Box-folder 43/27)
  - Hotel Licensure, 1971 (Box-folder 43/28)
  - Hill-Burton Community Service hearing, 1972 (Box-folder 44/1)
  - “Hobson Ambulance License Denial, Show Cause Hearing”, 1976 (Box-folder 44/2)
  - Hospital Rules Public Hearing, 1974 (Box-folder 44/3)
  - Huddleston, Jay, Variance petition, 1971 (Box-folder 44/4)
  - Humble Oil Variance Hearing, 1970 (Box-folder 44/5)
  - Karst Subdivision Court Action, 1973 (Box-folder 44/6)
  - LaSalle Hotel, Butte, 1975 (Box-folder 44/7)
  - Little Missouri, Notice of Public Hearing, 1974 (Box-folder 44/8)
  - Livingston, Open Burning Permit hearing, 1974 (Box-folder 44/9)
  - Lybeck’s Inc. (Feedlot) Hearing, Kalispell, 1977 (Box-folder 44/10)
  - Johns-Manville Corp. (Stillwater County), 1976 (Box-folder 44/11)
  - McIntyre Construction and S. Birch Inc., Variance Hearing, 1971 (Box-folder 44/12)
  - Measles, Hearing on Adoption of Rule to Control Outbreaks, 1979 (Box-folder 44/13)
  - Mike’s Service, Stipulation, 1976 (Box-folder 44/14)
  - Missoula, General Certificate of Need (transcript), 1978 (Box-folder 44/15)
  - “Missoula General, 1122 Review” Hearing (transcripts, photos, and slides), 1976 (Box-folder 44/16)
  - Montana Aqua Mobile Home Court (Joliet) (transcript), 1979 (Box-folder 44/17)
  - Montana-Dakota Utilities, Hearing on Variance And Renewal (transcript), 1973-1975 (Box-folder 44/18)
  - Montana Power Company (includes: transcripts for Corette plant Stack, Steam Electric generating plant, kV line hearings, Certificate of Need hearing), 1974-1979 (Box-folder 44/19-24)
  - Montana Sulfur and Chemical (Billings refinery Stack height), 1977 (Box-folder 44/25)
  - Motor Vehicle Wrecking Facilities and Junk Vehicle Disposal (Rule Amendment Hearing, transcript), 1976 (Box-folder 44/26)
  - Nuclear Logging Service Inc., Travel permit, 1976 (Box-folder 44/27)
  - Nursing Home License Revocation Hearings (Silver Bow Annex Nursing Home), 1972 (Box-folder 44/28)
  - Barry O’Leary Inc., Variance Hearing, 1971 (Box-folder 44/29)
  - Max Olive Subdivision, Findings of Fact, 1977 (Box-folder 44/30)
  - Pacific Silica, 1976 (Box-folder 44/31)
  - Peabody Coal Company, Big Sky Mine (Colstrip) (Water Discharge Permit), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 44/32)
  - Pfizer Inc., Variance, 1970 (Box-folder 44/33)
  - Philipsburg Garbage Dump, Court Action, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 44/34)
  - Philips Petroleum Variance Hearings (transcript), 1971-1975 (Box-folder 44/35)
  - Marriage Record Form, Amendment of Rule hearing, 1976 (Box-folder 44/36)
  - Recycle Contractors Inc., Court Papers, 1976 (Box-folder 44/37)
  - Richard Construction Variance Hearing, 1971 (Box-folder 44/38)
  - Riffe, George L. Hearing (transcript), 1973 (Box-folder 44/39)
  - Riverside Wrecking (Livingston), 1976 (Box-folder 44/40)
  - Rogers Motor Inn, Hearing (Revocation of License), 1972 (Box-folder 44/41)
  - City of Roundup, Variance request and hearing (re: landfill, transcript), 1974 (Box-folder 44/42)
  - Rudyard Hotel, Havre, 1973 (Box-folder 44/43)
  - Salish Hotel (Polson), “Legal Material”, 1973 (Box-folder 44/44)
  - Sanders County Memorial Hospital, hearing, 1974 (Box-folder 44/45)
  - Sidney Auto Wrecking, Show Cause Hearing, 1976 (Box-folder 44/46)
  - Refuse Disposal Areas, Hearings (Rules and Amendments), 1974, 1977 (Box-folder 44/47)
  - Sterling Hotel Hearing (Livingston) (transcript), 1975 (Box-folder 44/48)
  - Subdivision Review Hearing, 1977 (Box-folder 44/49)
  - Subdivision Review Fees and Solid Waste Disposal Plans, 1976 (Box-folder 44/50)
  - Subdivision Hearing (transcript), 1975 (Box-folder 44/51)
  - Thiel’s Trailer Court Hearing (transcript), 1975 (Box-folder 44/52)
  - Thompson Falls Lumber, Variance hearing (transcript), 1970 (Box-folder 44/53)
  - Hoerner-Waldorf, Variance and Petitions (transcript), 1970-1973 (Box-folder 45/1-4)
  - Stauffer Chemical Company, Variances and Renewals (transcript), 1970-1981 (Box-folder 45/5-7)
  - United Sierra, Cypress Mines, Variance hearings (transcript), 1970 (Box-folder 45/8)
  - “Volatile Organic Compounds Yellowstone County Final Action” (transcript), 1979 (Box-folder 45/9)
  - “Warm Springs State Hospital, LPN Collective Bargaining” (transcript), 1971 (Box-folder 45/10)
  - Dennis Washington Construction Company, Hearing (transcript), 1972 (Box-folder 45/11)
  - Water Quality, Construction Grants, 1973 (Box-folder 45/12)
  - Water Quality Standards, Use Classifications, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 45/13-16)
  - Water Pollution Control Program, State Grants (transcript), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 45/17)
  - Water Pollution, National Pollutant Discharge Elimination System hearing (transcript), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 45/18)
  - Water Supply, Ten Mile Drainage Compliance Schedule Hearing (transcript), 1979 (Box-folder 45/19)
  - Watuck Lodge (Cooke City) Hearing (transcript), 1976 (Box-folder 45/20)
  - Carl Weissman and Sons Wrecking Facility, Hearing (transcript), 1975 (Box-folder 45/21)
  - Women, Infants and Children (WIC) State Plan Hearing (transcript), 1979 (Box-folder 45/22)
  - Yellowstone and Missoula Counties, Local Air Pollution Control Programs (transcript), 1979 (Box-folder 45/23)
  - Yellowstone Pine Company hearing (transcript), 1975 (Box-folder 45/24)
  - American Petroleum Institute, “Comments…on Water Quality Criteria Proposed by U.S. EPA”, 1979 (Box-folder 46/1)
  - (State) Board of Health Meetings, 1968 July -1970 November (Box-folder 46/2-10)
  - Browning, Solid Waste Management System License hearing (transcript), 1988 (Box-folder 46/11)
  - Church Universal and Triumphant (CUT), Hearing On Draft EIS, and Final EIS, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 46/12-13)
  - Hospitals and Nursing Homes, Miscellaneous, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 46/14)
  - (State) Board of Health Meeting Materials (includes Concurrence documents), 1971 November–1978 October (Box-folder 48/1-14)
  - Air Quality, Hearings on Fluorides, Particulates, Open Burning Rules, and Threshold Limit Values (transcripts), 1971-1979 (Box-folder 49/1-7)
  - (State) Board of Health Meeting Materials, 1978 November - 1986 November (Box-folder 49/8-15)
  - State Implementation Plan Hearings (includes discussion of SO2 emissions in Anaconda, and Air Pollution Control Standards), 1972-1978 (Box-folder 49/16-20)
  - Sulfur Dioxide Emission Control Hearing (trans.), 1987 (Box-folder 49/21)
  - Surface Water Quality Standards/Criteria of Classifications Hearing (trans.), 1988 (Box-folder 49/22)
  - Air Quality, Hearings on Montana Ambient Air Quality Standards (MAAQS), 1967 (Box-folder 50/12-13)
  - (State) Board of Health Meeting (Agenda items, Minutes), 1991 August-October (Box-folder 51/10)
  - Montana Ambient Air Quality Standards (MAAQS) (Establishment, transcripts, etc.), 1967 (Box-folder 51/11-14)
  - Milk River Irrigators/City of Gillette, WY, 1987 (Box-folder 51/15)
  - Pegasus Gold, 1991 (Box-folder 51/16)
  - “Petition for Modification of Quality of Ambient Waters, Stillwater PGM Resources East Boulder Project, 1992 (Box-folder 51/17)
  - Railroad Tie Burning, 1991 (Box-folder 51/18)
  - Stillwater Mining Co., “Amendment #8 to Hard Rock Mining Permit” (Petition, Transcript, and Correspondence), 1991 (Box-folder 51/19)
  - Air Rules, Montana Quality Assurance Manual, 1991 (Box-folder 52/1)
  - Air Rules, Permit Fees Rules, 1991 (Box-folder 52/2)
  - Air Rules, Additions Comments re: Fees, 1991 (Box-folder 52/3)
  - (State) Board of Health Meetings (Agenda Items, Minutes, Supplemental docs, etc.), 1989 January -1991 November (Box-folder 52/4-10)
  - East Boulder Mine Project (Draft EIS and Supplement, Biological Assessment, Public Comments), 1991 (Box-folder 52/11-12)
  - Local Air Pollution Control Program, Flathead Co. (Court Papers, transcripts, approval), 1991 (Box-folder 52/13)
  - Local Air Pollution Control Program, Lincoln Co. (Application and approval), 1991 (Box-folder 52/14)
  - Local Air Pollution Control Program, Missoula Co. (Court papers, Exhibits, transcripts, application), 1991 (Box-folder 52/15-16)
  - Local Air Pollution Control Program, Silver Bow Co. (Court papers, transcripts), 1991 (Box-folder 52/17)
  - Brand “S” Lumber Citation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 53/13)
  - Butte/Silver Bow Air Quality Control Program, 1991 (Box-folder 53/14)
  - CENEX-EXXON (Farmer’s Union Central Exchange), 1980 (Box-folder 53/15)
  - Clark Fork Valley Appeal (Western Montana Nursing Home), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 53/16)
  - Max Olive Subdivision, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 53/17)
  - Noranda, Montanore Project (includes trans.), 1992 (Box-folder 53/18)
  - Stillwater Mining Company, Mine Expansion TPD (Draft Environmental Assessment), 1991 (Box-folder 53/19)
  - Stone Container Corp., Petitions for Amendment To Water Quality Permit, 1986 (Box-folder 53/20)
  - Water Quality Bureau, 401 Certification Rules, 1991 (Box-folder 53/21)
  - Water Quality Bureau, Connection Fees for Public Water, 1991 (Box-folder 53/22)
  - Yellowstone County, Volatile Organic Compounds Limit Rule, 1979 (Box-folder 53/23)
  - Adopting Rules for Ambient Air Quality, 1981 (Box-folder 54/1)
  - “Adoption of Rules Establishing Procedure for Public Comment for Air and Water Permits under Major Facilities Siting Act, 1980 (Box-folder 54/2)
  - Amend ARM, Public Water or Wastewater Systems, 1991 (Box-folder 54/3)
  - Amend ARM, Sulfur Oxide Emissions-Lead Smelters, 1991 (Box-folder 54/4)
  - Anaconda Copper Co., Appeal of Ambient Air Standards, 1981 (Box-folder 54/5)
  - Anaconda Company, Environmental Monitoring, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 54/6)
  - Amend ARM, Prohibiting Activities Affecting Water Quality, 1981 (Box-folder 54/7)
  - Amend ARM, Ambient Air re: Fluoride in Folage, 1981 (Box-folder 54/8)
  - Application, Western Energy for Air Quality Permit (Rosebud Mine), 1981-1984 (Box-folder 54/9)
  - CENEX, Appeal of Ambient Air Standards, 1981 (Box-folder 54/10)
  - EXXON, Appeal of Administrative Order re: Ambient Air Standards, 1991 (Box-folder 54/11)
  - Northern Plains Resources Council vs. Board of Health, Supreme Court (SC) Appeal #14215, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 54/12-14)
  - Northern Plains Resources Council vs. Board of Health, SC #14537, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 54/15)
  - Northern Plains Resources Council vs. Board of Health et. al., SC # 39228, 40462, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 54/16-18)
  - NPRC vs. Rosebud Co., SC # 8736, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 54/19)
  - W.R. Grace and Company, Variance Hearing, 1970 (Box-folder 55/3)
  - Adoption of Rules, Licensing of Labs, Performing Analysis of Public Water Systems, 1980 (Box-folder 55/4)
  - Amendments to Rules, Occupational Contaminants/Noise, Permits, 1980 (Box-folder 55/5)
  - Amendments to Rules, Surface Water Quality Standards, 1980 (Box-folder 55/6)
  - Anaconda Aluminum vs. Board of Health, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 55/7)
  - Anaconda Copper, Application for Renewal of Variance, 1980 (Box-folder 55/8)
  - Berg Lumber Company, Application for Open Burning exemption, 1980 (Box-folder 55/9)
  - Bozeman Blacktop, Application for Permit to Construct Batch Asphalt Plant, 1980 (Box-folder 55/10)
  - Burlington Northern Inc., Railroad Maintenance Facility (Whitefish), 1980 (Box-folder 55/11)
  - Conoco, Appeal from Administrative Order (Yellowstone Co.), 1980 (Box-folder 55/12)
  - Dugdale Construction Co., Appeal of Denial of Application for Air Quality Permit, 1980 (Box-folder 55/13)
  - Falls Chemical Company (Great Falls), 1980 (Box-folder 55/14)
  - Konitz Contracting, Air Quality Permit, 1982 (Box-folder 55/15)
  - Montana Power Company and Puget Sound Power and Light, Air Pollution Control Equipment, 1980 (Box-folder 55/16)
  - Mary Schendel Subdivision (Broadwater Co.), undated (Box-folder 55/17)
  - Stauffer Chemical Company (Silver Bow), Appeal Of Ambient Air Standards, 1981 (Box-folder 55/18)
  - St. Vincent Hospital, Appeal to Decision re: Expansion of hospital and care, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 55/19)
  - The Stillwater Protective Association and NPRC, Application for Declaratory Ruling, 1980 (Box-folder 55/20)
  - Board of Natural Resources and Conservation (BNRC), Bonneville Power Administration, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 55/21)
  - BNRC, 161 kV line (Bozeman-Dillon, Clyde Park- Dillon), 1981-1982 (Box-folder 55/22)
  - BNRC, Colstrip 3 and 4 (“Condition 12k”), 1976-1982 (Box-folder 55/23)
  - BNRC, Colstrip 3 and 4 (Court papers), 1980 (Box-folder 55/24)
  - BNRC, Colstrip 3 and 4 (Broadview-Colstrip kV line), 1980 (Box-folder 55/25)
  - BNRC, Colstrip 3 and 4 (Exhibits and Testimonies), 1976-1981 (Box-folder 55/26)
  - BNRC, Contract for Legal Services, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 56/1)
  - BNRC, Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 56/2)
  - BNRC, Fergus Electric/Montana Power (kV line), 1978 (Box-folder 56/3)
  - BNRC, Kootenai Falls (Court papers, includes reel- to-reel tape), 1982 (Box-folder 56/4)
  - BNRC, Lake Broadview Mitigation, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 56/5)
  - BNRC, Meeting Agendas and Documents, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 56/6-7)
  - BNRC, Miscellaneous, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 56/8-9)
  - BNRC, Resolutions, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 56/10)
  - Air Pollution Control, Missoula Program, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 56/11)
  - Air Pollution Control Regulations, Yellowstone County, 1984 (Box-folder 56/12)
  - Air Quality Permit, AEM Corporation, 1985 (Box-folder 56/13)
  - Air Quality Rules, 1985 (Box-folder 56/14)
  - Hazardous Waste, Memorandum of Agreement, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 56/15)
  - Hazardous Waste, Harlowton Solid Waste Management License, 1986 (Box-folder 56/16)
  - Hazardous Waste, Authorization and Rules, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 56/17)
  - Highway Department Variance (Asphalt Plants), 1981 (Box-folder 56/18)
  - Hobson Landfill, 1985 (Box-folder 56/19)
  - Immanuel Lutheran Home (Kalispell) (Construction of nursing home by Lantis), 1988 (Box-folder 56/20)
  - Ideal Cement, variance, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 56/21)
  - Inca Gold Corp. (includes Viking Mine near Powell), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 56/22)
  - Board of Health and Environmental Sciences, Meeting items, 1992 (Box-folder 59/16-17)
  - Air Quality Control Plan, Butte/Silver Bow, 1992 (Box-folder 59/18)
  - Air Quality Permit, Plum Creek, 1992 (Box-folder 59/19)
  - Air Quality Permit, Montana Resources (Butte), 1992 (Box-folder 59/20)
  - P-10 Emission Control Plan, Missoula, 1992 (Box-folder 59/21)
  - P-10 Emission Control Plan, Columbia Falls, 1992 (Box-folder 59/22)
  - Wood Placer Mine, Nevada Creek (Powell County), 1983 (Box-folder 59/23)
  - “401 Certification” (Pre-file documents, Depositions, Post-hearing comments), 1986 (Box-folder 60/1-6)
  - Air Quality Control Program, Missoula County, 1992 (Box-folder 60/7-8)
  - Air Quality Permit, Plum Creek Manufacturing (Evergreen), 1991 (Box-folder 60/9)
  - Air Quality Permit, Louisiana Pacific Corp (Missoula), 1992 (Box-folder 60/10)
  - Air Quality Bureau Hearing, Rule Amendment, 1992 (Box-folder 60/11)
  - “Amendment of Rules Dealing with MPDES and Pretreatment Rules, undated (Box-folder 60/12)
  - Board of Health, Meeting Items, 1992 March, May (Box-folder 60/13-14)
  - BHES, Dennis Schreffler M.D., 1992 (Box-folder 60/15-16)
  - BNRC, Meeting Items, 1988 March-November (Box-folder 61/2-9)
  - BHES, Adoption of Rules, Local Water Quality Districts, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 62/1)
  - BHES, Air Quality Issues (specifically Oxygenated Fuels, liquid De-Icer, and Billings Sulfur Dioxide), 1993 (Box-folder 62/2)
  - BHES, Air Quality Permit Fees, 1992 (Box-folder 62/3)
  - BHES, “Exxon Company’s Comment re: Missoula’s Oxygenated Fuels Regulations”, 1992 (Box-folder 62/4)
  - BHES, “Minimum Standards for On-site Subsurface Wastewater Treatment”, 1992 (Box-folder 62/5)
  - BHES, Missoula Carbon Monoxide Control Program, 1992 (Box-folder 62/6)
  - BHES, Missoula Oxygenated Fuels, 1992 (Box-folder 62/7)
  - BHES, Montana SIP, “Stationary Source Technical And Environmental Compliance Assistance Program, 1992 (Box-folder 62/8)
  - BHES, Noranda, Montanore Project Petition for Change in Ambient Water Quality, 1992 (Box-folder 62/9)
  - BHES, Montgomery Construction, Air Quality Permit, 1992 (Box-folder 62/10)
  - BHES, “Non-degradation Petitions of Noranda’s Montanore Project and ASARCO Rock Creek Project, 1993 (Box-folder 62/11)
  - BHES, Open Burning Permit Fees, 1992 (Box-folder 62/12)
  - BHES, Park County Refuse Disposal District No. 1, 1993 (Box-folder 62/13)
  - BHES, Plum Creek Manufacturing, Air Quality Permit, 1992 (Box-folder 62/14)
  - BHES, Review of Small Water and Sewer Systems, 1992 (Box-folder 62/15)
  - BHES, State Health Plan Update, circa 1992 (Box-folder 62/16)
  - BHES, Stillwater Mining/Stillwater PGM Resources, East Boulder Project, Nye mine, 1992 (Box-folder 62/17-22)
  - BHES, Sun River Valley School (Public Water Supply System), 1993 (Box-folder 62/23)
  - BHES, Water Quality Rules, Revisions and Amendments, 1992 (Box-folder 62/24)
  - BHES, Water Quality Standards and Non- degradation Policy, 1992 (Box-folder 62/25)
  - BHES, Yellowstone County Air Pollution Control Program, 1992 (Box-folder 62/26)
  - “Solid Waste Program Report on SWM Plan, Proposal/Timeline”, undated (Box-folder 62/27)
  - Surface Water Quality Non-degradation, 1992 (Box-folder 62/28-29)
  - Surface Water Quality, Responses to Written Public Comments, circa 1992 (Box-folder 62/30)
  - Water Quality Bureau, Water Works and Sewage System Standards, 1992 (Box-folder 62/31)
  - Water Quality Bureau, Public Comments to WQB Circular, 1992 (Box-folder 62/32)
  - ASARCO Air Quality Permit Violation, 1993 (Box-folder 63/1)
  - BHES, Air Quality Bureau Consideration of Collecting Fees from Sulfur Dioxide Emitting Industries near Laurel/Billings, 1993 (Box-folder 63/2)
  - BHES, Billings Indian Health Service, 1993 (Box-folder 63/3)
  - BHES, Granite County Memorial Hospital, Non-compliance, 1993 (Box-folder 63/4)
  - BHES, Libby PM-10 Emission Inventory, Base Year 1986-1987, Final Report, 1993 (Box-folder 63/5)
  - BHES, Meeting Items, 1993 January -1993 November (Box-folder 63/6-17)
  - Adoption of Rules, re: Asbestos control, 1989 (Box-folder 64/1)
  - Adoption of Rules, re: Licensing of Underground Storage Tank Installers and Inspectors, 1999 (Box-folder 64/2)
  - Adoption of Rules, re: Underground Storage Tanks and reimbursement for Petroleum Storage Tank Release Clean-ups, 1989 (Box-folder 64/3)
  - Amendment of ARM, re: Mining Waste Exclusions, 1990 (Box-folder 64/4)
  - Amendment of ARM, Boiler and Industrial Furnace, 1992 (Box-folder 64/5-6)
  - BHES, Meeting Items, 1993 November (Box-folder 64/7-9)
  - BHES, Middlefork Auto Restoration Motor Vehicle Wrecking Facility (Essex), 1993 (Box-folder 64/10-12)
  - BHES, Lincoln County Air Quality Control Program, 1993 (Box-folder 64/13)
  - BHES, State Health Plan for Ambulatory Circulatory Centers, 1993 (Box-folder 64/14)
  - BHES, Water Quality Districts Rule Comments, 1993 (Box-folder 64/15)
  - BHES, Western Area Power Administration, Upgrading of kV line between Fort Peck and Wolf Point, 1993 (Box-folder 64/16)
  - Church Universal and Triumphant (CUT), re: Proposed Developments in Park County, 1993 (Box-folder 64/17-18)
  - “Public Comments Received…re: Proposed Amendments and New Rules on Non-degradation and Surface Water Quality Standards, Vol. I and II, 1993 (Box-folder 64/19-20)
  - Air Quality Bureau (AQB), Ambient Air Standards, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 65/9)
  - AQB, Agreement between DHES and Department Of Natural Resources, 1973 (Box-folder 65/10)
  - AQB, Air Regulations, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 65/11)
  - AQB, The Maronick Company (Agreement on Air Pollution Monitoring Site), 1972 (Box-folder 65/12)
  - AQB, Miscellaneous, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 65/13)
  - AQB, Proposed Air Pollution Regulations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 65/14)
  - AQB, “Oil Refineries Petitions and Briefs re: Air rules”, 1968-1977 (Box-folder 65/15-16)
  - Amendment or Rule, Conditions for Issuance of Air Quality Permits (includes trans.), 1982 (Box-folder 65/17)
  - BHES, Laser Energy Restrictions and Occupational Noise/Air Contaminants, 1980 (Box-folder 65/18)
  - “Declaratory Ruling (Reg./Anaconda) (includes trans.), 1981 (Box-folder 65/19)
  - Eastalco Aluminum Company (Maryland), re: Fluorides, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 65/20-21)
  - Fluoride in Forage (includes trans.), 1981 (Box-folder 65/22)
  - Garlick’s Helicopters, “Investigation and Imminent And Substantial Danger to Public Health or the Environment, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 65/23)
  - “MAAQS – Litigation”, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 65/24)
  - MAAQS, Air Rules, 1986 (Box-folder 65/25)
  - MAAQS, Discussion of Fluoride, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 65/26)
  - Montana Sulfur and Chemical Company, Air Quality, 1970 (Box-folder 65/27)
  - Air Quality Rules, PM-10 Emissions, 1988 (Box-folder 66/20)
  - Repeal of Rules, re: Prevention of Significant Deterioration (PSD), 1982 (Box-folder 66/21)
  - SO2 Legislation and DHES Testimony, 1987 (Box-folder 66/22)
  - Yellowstone Valley Citizens’ Council (re: Billings SO2), 1986 (Box-folder 66/23)